Guide to the Archives Foreign File (AFF), Section 4
Archives Foreign File (AFF), Section 4
- Box: 72, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 72, Folder 5)
  - Item 9: Biographical Sketch - Len Hope, Publication (Box 72, Folder 5)
  - Item 10: Biographical Sketch - Camil bisson, Publication (Box 72, Folder 5)
  - Item 11: Biographical Sketch - Dawn Cartwright, Publication (Box 72, Folder 5)
  - Item 12: Biographical Sketch - Tom Dottilo, Publication (Box 72, Folder 5)
  - Item 13: Biographical Sketch - Buddy Kitchen, Publication (Box 72, Folder 5)
  - Item 14: Biographical Sketch - Marilynne Lesperance, Publication (Box 72, Folder 5)
  - Item 15: Biographical Sketch - Lorna Moses, Publication (Box 72, Folder 5)
  - Item 16: Biographical Sketch - Bill Murninghan, Publication (Box 72, Folder 5)
  - Item 17: Biographical Sketch - Tom Murphy, Publication (Box 72, Folder 5)
  - Item 18: Biographical Sketch - Ron Pellerin, Publication (Box 72, Folder 5)
  - Item 19: Biogrpahical Sketch - Bert Rovers, Publication (Box 72, Folder 5)
  - Item 20: Biographical Sketch - Greg Spencer, Publication (Box 72, Folder 5)
- Box: 72, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 72, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Election '99: Which side are you on?, Publication (Box 72, Folder 6)
    Notes: flyer
  - Item 2: Election '99: Which side are you on?, Publication (Box 72, Folder 6)
  - Item 3: Election '99: Which side are you on?, Publication (Box 72, Folder 6)
  - Item 4: You can vote and take back Ontario, Publication (Box 72, Folder 6)
  - Item 5: You can vote and take back Ontario, Publication (Box 72, Folder 6)
  - Item 6: You can vote and take back Ontario, Publication (Box 72, Folder 6)
- Box: 72, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 72, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Democracy and vision: What's really at issue in the CAW-SEIU-CLCL Dispute, Publication (Box 72, Folder 7)
    Notes: article; photocopy
  - Item 2: Open Letter to progressive labour activists on the CAW-CLC-SEIU Dispute, Publication (Box 72, Folder 7)
  - Item 3: False solutions, growing protests: Recapturing the agenda: National Collective Bargaining & Political Action Convention, Toronto, June 4-June 7, 1996, Publication (Box 72, Folder 7)
    Author: CAW-Canada
- Box: 72, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 72, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: The CAW it's your best bet, Publication (Box 72, Folder 8)
  - Item 2: A shipbuilding policy for Canada, 1998; Publication (Box 72, Folder 8)
    Author: CAW- Canada
  - Item 3: The Threats and opportunities of airline restructuring, 1999; Publication (Box 72, Folder 8)
  - Item 4: Presentation to the House of Commons Standing Committee on Transportation, 1999; Publication (Box 72, Folder 8)
  - Item 5: $70 Million: another drop in the bucket, Publication (Box 72, Folder 8)
  - Item 6: Canada needs a shipbuilding policy!, Publication (Box 72, Folder 8)
  - Item 7: Canada needs a shipbuilding policy!, Publication (Box 72, Folder 8)
  - Item 8: The Harris Government is undermining the manufacturing base of Ontario, Publication (Box 72, Folder 8)
  - Item 9: The Harris Government is undermining the manufacturing base of Ontario, Publication (Box 72, Folder 8)
  - Item 10: National Child Care. NOW!, Publication (Box 72, Folder 8)
  - Item 11: National Child Care. NOW!, Publication (Box 72, Folder 8)
- Box: 72, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 72, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Ever thought of taking a family holiday with your union?, Publication (Box 72, Folder 9)
- Box: 72, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 72, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: CAW proposals on hazardous substances meeting with the Honourable Jim Flaherty Ministry of Labour, Publication (Box 72, Folder 10)
  - Item 2: Holmes Insultations Limited, Sarnia, on history of the Plant visits made - request from Dr. martin's Office, Feb. 11, 1975, Publication (Box 72, Folder 10)
  - Item 3: Second Hand Smoke: Butt it out, Publication (Box 72, Folder 10)
  - Item 4: Second Hand Smoke: Butt it out, Publication (Box 72, Folder 10)
  - Item 5: Second Hand Smoke: Butt it out, Publication (Box 72, Folder 10)
  - Item 6: Fight speed-up, 1995; Publication (Box 72, Folder 10)
  - Item 7: Devil of a poison, 1999; Publication (Box 72, Folder 10)
  - Item 8: Devil of a poison, 1999; Publication (Box 72, Folder 10)
- Box: 72, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 72, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Cancer causing substances: a worker's guide to understanding and eliminating them from the work environment: a document prepared by the Occupational Health Clinics for Ontario Workers (OHCOW) in cooperation with and for the Canadian Auto Workers (CAW), Publication (Box 72, Folder 11)
    Notes: pt.1
- Box: 72, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 72, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Cancer causing substances: a worker's guide to understanding and eliminating them from the work environment: a document prepared by the Occupational Health Clinics for Ontario Workers (OHCOW) in cooperation with and for the Canadian Auto Workers (CAW), Publication (Box 72, Folder 12)
    Notes: pt.2
- Box: 72, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 72, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: CAW/Bombardier de Havilland, 1997; Publication (Box 72, Folder 13)
  - Item 2: CAW/Bombardier de Havilland, 1997; Publication (Box 72, Folder 13)
  - Item 3: CAW-Canada/CAMI: Report, 1995; Publication (Box 72, Folder 13)
  - Item 4: CAW/CN Rail: Report, 1998; Publication (Box 72, Folder 13)
    Notes: Aug.
- Box: 72, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 72, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Mine Mill Smelter Workers CAW Local 598, 1997; Publication (Box 72, Folder 14)
- Box: 72, Folder: 15, Publication (Box 72, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: The CAW is working people like you, Publication (Box 72, Folder 15)
  - Item 2: Getting leaner & meaner, 1996; Publication (Box 72, Folder 15)
    Notes: Summer
- Box: 72, Folder: 16, Publication (Box 72, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Fighting for Canada's public pension system, 1996; Publication (Box 72, Folder 16)
- Box: 72, Folder: 17, Publication (Box 72, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: National and Area Staff Reports to CAW Council: Sheraton Centre Hotel, Toronto, Ontario, December 3-5, 1999, Publication (Box 72, Folder 17)
- Box: 72, Folder: 18, Publication (Box 72, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Long-term contracts-the new concession, Publication (Box 72, Folder 18)
  - Item 2: Long-term contracts-the new concession, Publication (Box 72, Folder 18)
  - Item 3: The Red Book, 1994; Publication (Box 72, Folder 18)
    Notes: advertisement / flyer
  - Item 4: More time for ourselves, our children, our community, 1993; Publication (Box 72, Folder 18)
- Box: 72, Folder: 19, Publication (Box 72, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: CAW Council speech of Basil "Buzz" Hargrove, President: August 20-22, 1999, Publication (Box 72, Folder 19)
  - Item 2: Speech by CAW President Buz Hargrove to the Collective Bargaining and Political Action Convention: Sheraton Centre Hotel, June 8-11, 1999, Publication (Box 72, Folder 19)
- Box: 72, Folder: 20, Publication (Box 72, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: The Union: National Newspaper of the CAW, 1995; Publication (Box 72, Folder 20)
  - Item 2: The Union: National Newspaper of the CAW, 1995; Publication (Box 72, Folder 20)
  - Item 3: The Union: National Newspaper of the CAW, 1996; Publication (Box 72, Folder 20)
  - Item 4: The Union: National Newspaper of the CAW, 1996; Publication (Box 72, Folder 20)
- Box: 72, Folder: 21, Publication (Box 72, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: Employment Equity: a commitment to equality, Publication (Box 72, Folder 21)
  - Item 2: This ain't going away, 1997; Publication (Box 72, Folder 21)
  - Item 3: This ain't going away, 1997; Publication (Box 72, Folder 21)
  - Item 4: This ain't going away, 1997; Publication (Box 72, Folder 21)
  - Item 5: This ain't going away, 1997; Publication (Box 72, Folder 21)
  - Item 6: The CAW and childcare, 1995; Publication (Box 72, Folder 21)
  - Item 7: Building the union: Women's Committees in the CAW, 1995; Publication (Box 72, Folder 21)
- Box: 72, Folder: 22, Publication (Box 72, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: Constitution of the British Columbia Federation of Labour, C.L.C., 2004; Publication (Box 72, Folder 22)
    Author: British Columbia Federation of Labour (C.L.C.)
  - Item 2: Constitution of the British Columbia Federation of Labour, C.L.C., 1998; Publication (Box 72, Folder 22)
  - Item 3: Constitution of the British Columbia Federation of Labour, C.L.C., 2000; Publication (Box 72, Folder 22)
  - Item 4: Constitution of the British Columbia Federation of Labour, C.L.C., 1990; Publication (Box 72, Folder 22)
  - Item 5: Constitution of the British Columbia Federation of Labour, C.L.C., 2004; Publication (Box 72, Folder 22)
  - Item 6: Constitution of the British Columbia Federation of Labour, C.L.C., 2004; Publication (Box 72, Folder 22)
  - Item 7: Constitution of the British Columbia Federation of Labour, C.L.C., 1990; Publication (Box 72, Folder 22)
  - Item 8: Constitution of the British Columbia Federation of Labour, C.L.C., 2002; Publication (Box 72, Folder 22)
  - Item 9: Constitution of the British Columbia Federation of Labour, C.L.C., 1998; Publication (Box 72, Folder 22)
  - Item 10: Constitution of the British Columbia Federation of Labour, C.L.C., 2000; Publication (Box 72, Folder 22)
  - Item 11: Constitution of the British Columbia Federation of Labour, C.L.C., 2006; Publication (Box 72, Folder 22)
- Box: 72, Folder: 23, Publication (Box 72, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: A future that works for everyone, 2000; Publication (Box 72, Folder 23)
    Notes: photocopy; looseleaf
- Box: 72, Folder: 24, Publication (Box 72, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: A future that works for everyone, 2000; Publication (Box 72, Folder 24)
- Box: 72, Folder: 25, Publication (Box 72, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: Constitution of the Canadian Labour Congress = Statuts du Congre`s du Travail du Canada, 1976; Publication (Box 72, Folder 25)
    Author: Canadian Labour Congress
    Language: English; French.
  - Item 2: Constitution of the Canadian Labour Congress = Statuts du Congre`s du travail du Canada, 1996; Publication (Box 72, Folder 25)
  - Item 3: Constitution of the Canadian Labour Congress = Statuts du Congre`s du travail du Canada, 1999; Publication (Box 72, Folder 25)
  - Item 4: Constitution of the Canadian Labour Congress = Statuts du Congre`s du travail du Canada, 1999; Publication (Box 72, Folder 25)
  - Item 5: Constitution of the Canadian Labour Congress = Statuts du Congre`s du travail du Canada, 1990; Publication (Box 72, Folder 25)
- Box: 72, Folder: 26, Publication (Box 72, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: Constitution of the Canadian Labour Congress = Statuts du Congre`s du travail du Canada, 1999; Publication (Box 72, Folder 26)
  - Item 2: Constitution of the Canadian Labour Congress = Statuts du Congre`s du travail du Canada, 1992; Publication (Box 72, Folder 26)
  - Item 3: Constitution of the Canadian Labour Congress = Statuts du Congre`s du travail du Canada, 1994; Publication (Box 72, Folder 26)
- Box: 72, Folder: 27, Publication (Box 72, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: Welcome to the 23rd Canadian Labour Congress Convention!, 2002; Publication (Box 72, Folder 27)
  - Item 2: Resolutions: Nineteenth Constitutional Convention, Vancouver, June 1992, Publication (Box 72, Folder 27)
- Box: 72, Folder: 28, Publication (Box 72, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: School workers health and safety guide, 1996; Publication (Box 72, Folder 28)
    Author: Canadian Centre for Occupational Health and Safety; Quantum System 2000 (Firm)
- Box: 72, Folder: 29, Publication (Box 72, Folder 29)
  - Item 1: Pay equity, CTEA representative's guide, 1993; Publication (Box 72, Folder 29)
    Author: Canadian Telephone Employees' Association
  - Item 2: Pay equity, CTEA representative's guide, 1993; Publication (Box 72, Folder 29)
- Box: 72, Folder: 30, Publication (Box 72, Folder 30)
  - Item 1: Constitution, 2009; Publication (Box 72, Folder 30)
    Author: Canadian Union of Public Employees
  - Item 2: Constitution, 1991; Publication (Box 72, Folder 30)
  - Item 3: Constitution, 1993; Publication (Box 72, Folder 30)
  - Item 4: Constitution, 2001; Publication (Box 72, Folder 30)
  - Item 5: Constitution, 2003; Publication (Box 72, Folder 30)
  - Item 6: Constitution, 2005; Publication (Box 72, Folder 30)
  - Item 7: Constitution, 2007; Publication (Box 72, Folder 30)
  - Item 8: Statuts, 1991; Publication (Box 72, Folder 30)
    Notes:
- Box: 73, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 73, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: National President's Report to the National Executive Board, 2002; Publication (Box 73, Folder 1)
    Notes: Feb. 26-28
  - Item 2: National President's Report to the National Executive Board, 2002; Publication (Box 73, Folder 1)
    Notes: May 15-17
  - Item 3: National President's Report to the National Executive Board, 2002; Publication (Box 73, Folder 1)
    Notes: Sept. 24-26
  - Item 4: National President's Report to the National Executive Board, 2002; Publication (Box 73, Folder 1)
    Notes: Dec. 11-12
  - Item 5: Contracting out gets failing grade:, 1998; Publication (Box 73, Folder 1)
    Author: Canadian Union of Public Employees. Local 474
    Notes: article
  - Item 6: Contracting out gets failing grade:, 1998; Publication (Box 73, Folder 1)
- Box: 73, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 73, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Statutes and by-laws of the CSN: including the amendments made by the 1990 Convention, 1990-1992 (Box 73, Folder 2)
    Author: Confederation des syndicats nationaux
  - Item 2: Statutes and by-laws of the CSN: including the amendments made by the 1990 Convention, 1992; Publication (Box 73, Folder 2)
    Notes: 1990-1992
- Box: 73, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 73, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Trade union agreement between Kimberly-Clark Inc., St. Catharines and IWA-Canada, Local 1-92-4: 1992-1995, Publication (Box 73, Folder 3)
    Author: International Woodworkers of America-Canada
    Notes: 1992-1995
- Box: 73, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 73, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Statement of Mac A. Fleming in response to terrorist attack, Publication (Box 73, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: Canada needs a shipbuilding policy!, Publication (Box 73, Folder 4)
    Author: Shipyards General Workers Federation
- Box: 73, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 73, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Program, President's Report & Constitution: 43rd Convention: New Brunswick Federation of Labour, June 4, 5, 6 & 7, 2000, Edmundston, NB, Publication (Box 73, Folder 5)
    Author: New Brunswick Federation of Labour
- Box: 73, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 73, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Office ergonomics workbook, 1997; Publication (Box 73, Folder 6)
    Author: Occupational Health Clinics for Ontario Workers Inc.
- Box: 73, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 73, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Constitution = Statuts, 1995; Publication (Box 73, Folder 7)
    Author: Ontario Federation of Labour
  - Item 2: Constitution = Statuts, 1997; Publication (Box 73, Folder 7)
  - Item 3: Constitution = Statuts, 2001; Publication (Box 73, Folder 7)
  - Item 4: Constitution, 2001; Publication (Box 73, Folder 7)
  - Item 5: Constitution, 2001; Publication (Box 73, Folder 7)
  - Item 6: Constitution = Statuts, 2005; Publication (Box 73, Folder 7)
  - Item 7: Constitution, 1993; Publication (Box 73, Folder 7)
  - Item 8: Constitution = Statuts, 1991; Publication (Box 73, Folder 7)
- Box: 73, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 73, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Ontario Federation of Labour: 50th Anniversary, 1957-2007 (Box 73, Folder 8)
    Notes: magazine
- Box: 73, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 73, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: 5th Biennial Convention"Occupational disease shifting the burden", 1999; Publication (Box 73, Folder 9)
    Notes: document 1
  - Item 2: 5th Biennial Convention"Decent work in a decent society", 1999; Publication (Box 73, Folder 9)
    Notes: document 2
  - Item 3: 5th Biennial Convention"Decent work in a decent society", 1999; Publication (Box 73, Folder 9)
  - Item 4: 5th Biennial Convention"Fighting the right and building our vision", 1999; Publication (Box 73, Folder 9)
    Notes: document 3
  - Item 5: 5th Biennial Convention"Fighting the right and building our vision", 1999; Publication (Box 73, Folder 9)
  - Item 6: 5th Biennial Convention"Your health, your future, your life our vision for the Health Care in Ontario", 1999; Publication (Box 73, Folder 9)
    Notes: document 4
  - Item 7: 5th Biennial Convention"Your health, your future, your life our vision for the Health Care in Ontario", 1999; Publication (Box 73, Folder 9)
  - Item 8: 5th Biennial Convention"The Erosion of human rights in Ontario, Educating & Organizing for the 21st Century", 1999; Publication (Box 73, Folder 9)
    Notes: document 5
  - Item 9: 5th Biennial Convention"Privatization: Private gain at public expense", 1999; Publication (Box 73, Folder 9)
    Notes: document 6
  - Item 10: 5th Biennial Convention"Privatization: Private gain at public expense", 1999; Publication (Box 73, Folder 9)
  - Item 11: Ontarion Federation of Labour - 5th Biennial Convention -- [President's Report; Secretary-Treasurer's Report; Executive Vice-President's Report], 1999; Publication (Box 73, Folder 9)
    Notes: Nov. 22-26
  - Item 12: Ontario Federation of Labour, 6th Biennial Convention, Dec. 3-7, 2001: Convention Report, Publication (Box 73, Folder 9)
  - Item 13: Ontario Federation of Labour, 6th Biennial Convention, Dec. 3-7, 2001: Convention Report, Publication (Box 73, Folder 9)
- Box: 73, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 73, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Ontarion Federation of Labour - 5th Biennial Convention -- [President's Report; Secretary-Treasurer's Report; Executive Vice-President's Report], 1999; Publication (Box 73, Folder 10)
  - Item 2: Policy document: December 3-7, 2001: Activism, Sheraton Centre, Toronto, Ontario, Canada, Publication (Box 73, Folder 10)
  - Item 3: OFL Action Plan: as amended December 5, 2001, Publication (Box 73, Folder 10)
  - Item 4: Persons with disabilities labour's view: as amended December 3, 2001, Publication (Box 73, Folder 10)
  - Item 5: Persons with disabilities labour's view: as amended December 3, 2001, Publication (Box 73, Folder 10)
  - Item 6: The Privatization of Ontario's Education System :1995-2001: OFL Education is a Right Task Force Report on Publicly-Funded Education in Ontario, Publication (Box 73, Folder 10)
  - Item 7: The Privatization of Ontario's Education System :1995-2001: OFL Education is a Right Task Force Report on Publicly-Funded Education in Ontario, Publication (Box 73, Folder 10)
  - Item 8: OFL Action Plan: as amended December 5, 2001, Publication (Box 73, Folder 10)
  - Item 9: Policy resolutions: 1997-2001, Publication (Box 73, Folder 10)
- Box: 73, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 73, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Policy document: December 3-7, 2001: Activism, Sheraton Centre, Toronto, Ontario, Canada, Publication (Box 73, Folder 11)
  - Item 2: Ontario Federation of Labour: 1990 Programme Activities Report, Publication (Box 73, Folder 11)
  - Item 3: Ontario Federation of Labour: 1990 Programme Activities Report, Publication (Box 73, Folder 11)
  - Item 4: Ontario Federation of Labour: 1990 Programme Activities Report, Publication (Box 73, Folder 11)
  - Item 5: Ontario Federation of Labour: 1990 Programme Activities Report, 1992; Publication (Box 73, Folder 11)
  - Item 6: Ontario Federation of Labour: 1990 Programme Activities Report, 1992; Publication (Box 73, Folder 11)
  - Item 7: 5th Biennial Convention: Building for Tomorrow Together, November 22-26, 1999, Publication (Box 73, Folder 11)
    Notes: Document 1
- Box: 73, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 73, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Policy and procedures manual: 1999/2000, Publication (Box 73, Folder 12)
    Author: Ontario Secondary School Teachers' Federation
  - Item 2: Policy and procedures manual: 2000/2001, Publication (Box 73, Folder 12)
  - Item 3: Policy and procedures manual: 2001/2002, Publication (Box 73, Folder 12)
- Box: 73, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 73, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Salary Grid: Ontario Secondary School Teachers' Federation, 1998-1999 (Box 73, Folder 13)
  - Item 2: Salary Grid: Ontario Secondary School Teachers' Federation, 1999-2000 (Box 73, Folder 13)
- Box: 73, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 73, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Salary Grid: Keewatin-Partricia - Teachers, 1998-1999 (Box 73, Folder 14)
  - Item 2: Salary Grid: Keewatin-Partricia - Teachers, 1999-2000 (Box 73, Folder 14)
  - Item 3: Rates of pay: Casual Teacher, 1998-2000 (Box 73, Folder 14)
  - Item 4: Rates of pay: Casual Teacher, 1998-2000 (Box 73, Folder 14)
  - Item 5: Salary Grid: Kawartha Pine Ridge, 1998-1999 (Box 73, Folder 14)
  - Item 6: Salary Grid: Kawartha Pine Ridge, 1999-2000 (Box 73, Folder 14)
  - Item 7: Rate of Pay: Lakehead - SESP Public, 1998-1999 (Box 73, Folder 14)
  - Item 8: Salary Grid: Lakehead, 1998-1999 (Box 73, Folder 14)
  - Item 9: Salary Grid: Lakehead, 1999-2000 (Box 73, Folder 14)
- Box: 73, Folder: 15, Publication (Box 73, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Salary Grid: Grand Erie, 1998-1999 (Box 73, Folder 15)
  - Item 2: Salary Grid: Grand Erie, 1999-2000 (Box 73, Folder 15)
  - Item 3: Rates of Pay: Greater Essex, 1998-1999 (Box 73, Folder 15)
  - Item 4: Rates of Pay: Greater Essex, 1999-2000 (Box 73, Folder 15)
  - Item 5: Salary Grid: Halton, 1998-1999 (Box 73, Folder 15)
  - Item 6: Salary Grid: Halton, 1999-2000 (Box 73, Folder 15)
  - Item 7: Salary Grid: Hamilton-Wentworth, 1998-1999 (Box 73, Folder 15)
  - Item 8: Salary Grid: Hamilton-Wentworth, 1999-2000 (Box 73, Folder 15)
  - Item 9: Salary Grid: Hastings and Prince Edward, 1998-1999 (Box 73, Folder 15)
  - Item 10: Salary Grid: Hastings and Prince Edward, 1999-2000 (Box 73, Folder 15)
- Box: 73, Folder: 16, Publication (Box 73, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Rate of pay: Niagara, 1998-1999 (Box 73, Folder 16)
  - Item 2: Rate of pay: Niagara, 1999-2000 (Box 73, Folder 16)
  - Item 3: Salary Grid: Niagara, 1998-1999 (Box 73, Folder 16)
  - Item 4: Salary Grid: Niagara, 1999-2000 (Box 73, Folder 16)
  - Item 5: Rates of pay: Near North, 1998-1999 (Box 73, Folder 16)
  - Item 6: Rates of pay: Near North, 1999-2000 (Box 73, Folder 16)
  - Item 7: Salary Grid: Near North, 1998-1999 (Box 73, Folder 16)
  - Item 8: Salary Grid: Near North, 1999-2000 (Box 73, Folder 16)
  - Item 9: Salary Grid: Ottawa-Carleton, 1998-1999 (Box 73, Folder 16)
  - Item 10: Salary Grid: Ottawa-Carleton, 1999-2000 (Box 73, Folder 16)
- Box: 73, Folder: 17, Publication (Box 73, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Salary Grid: Peel, 1998-1999 (Box 73, Folder 17)
  - Item 2: Salary Grid: Peel, 1999-2000 (Box 73, Folder 17)
  - Item 3: Salary Grid: Rainbow, 1999-2001 (Box 73, Folder 17)
  - Item 4: Salary Grid: Rainbow, 1998-1999 (Box 73, Folder 17)
  - Item 5: Salary Grid: Rainbow, 1999-2000 (Box 73, Folder 17)
  - Item 6: Salary Grid: Rainy River, 1998-1999 (Box 73, Folder 17)
  - Item 7: Salary Grid: Rainy River, 1999-2000 (Box 73, Folder 17)
  - Item 8: Salary Grid: Renfrew, 1998-1999 (Box 73, Folder 17)
  - Item 9: Salary Grid: Renfrew, 1999-2000 (Box 73, Folder 17)
- Box: 73, Folder: 18, Publication (Box 73, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Salary Grid: Simcoe, 1998-1999 (Box 73, Folder 18)
  - Item 2: Salary Grid: Simcoe, 1999-2000 (Box 73, Folder 18)
  - Item 3: Salary Grid: St. Clair, 1998-2000 (Box 73, Folder 18)
  - Item 4: Salary Grid: Toronto, 1998-1999 (Box 73, Folder 18)
  - Item 5: Salary Grid: Toronto, 1999-2000 (Box 73, Folder 18)
  - Item 6: Salary Grid: Trillium Lakelands, 1998-1999 (Box 73, Folder 18)
  - Item 7: Salary Grid: Trillium Lakelands, 1999-2000 (Box 73, Folder 18)
  - Item 8: Salary Grid: Upper Canada, 1998-1999 (Box 73, Folder 18)
  - Item 9: Salary Grid: Upper Canada, 1999-2000 (Box 73, Folder 18)
  - Item 10: Salary Grid: Waterloo, 1998-1999 (Box 73, Folder 18)
  - Item 11: Salary Grid: Waterloo, 1999-2000 (Box 73, Folder 18)
  - Item 12: Salary Grid: Upper Canada, 1998-1999 (Box 73, Folder 18)
  - Item 13: Salary Grid: Upper Canada, 1999-2000 (Box 73, Folder 18)
- Box: 73, Folder: 19, Publication (Box 73, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Handbook, 1991-1992 (Box 73, Folder 19)